CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTION
本剧中的人物、地点、组织 和事件均属虚构
ADMISSION TICKET TITLE: SONAGI
门票 名称：SONAGI
What is this?
这是什么？
Do you have time this weekend?
这个周末你有时间吗？
Let's go watch a movie.
我们去看电影吧。
I have something for you.
我有东西给你。
What?
什么？
What is this?
这是什么？
I bought it because I liked it.
我买它是因为我喜欢它。
Is beautiful.
是美丽的。
Euijeong, Gicheul. Look here.
义正、吉哲尔. 看这里。
There's no need to.
没必要。
Next. Let's do one.
下一个。我们来做一个吧。
One two Three.
一二三。
Can you do one more thing?
你还能再做一件事吗？
So that we both have our own.
这样我们就有了自己的。
Gicheul. You don't even try to hide it.
吉舍尔。你甚至不试图隐藏它。
One two...
一二...
Wait a minute.
等一下。
I'll strap it on for you.
我会为你系上它。
-Please. -Thanks.
-请。 -谢谢。
One two Three.
一二三。
One more thing?
还有一件事？
Come closer.
靠近点。
Ready?
准备好？
ABSOLUTE EVIL
绝对的邪恶
One two Three.
一二三。
I haven't seen Junmo in a long time.
好久没见到君莫了。
He's very busy.
他很忙。
Why? You miss him?
为什么？你想他了？
Of course.
当然。
He's my only son-in-law.
他是我唯一的女婿。
I'll tell him to check here.
我会告诉他到这里检查一下。
Tell him to go on TV shows
叫他上 电视节目
like other detectives do.
就像其他侦探一样。
I also want to brag about my son-in-law, like other ladies here.
我也想像这里的其他女士一样夸耀我的女婿。
Mom, do you remember that kid
妈妈，你还记得那个孩子吗？
Jung Gicheula, from my church choir?
Jung Gicheula，来自我的教堂唱诗班？
Of course.
当然。
Apparently he became a gangster.
显然他变成了黑帮。
Did you know about that too?
你也知道这件事吗？
Living in one place for 20 years,
在一个地方生活了20年，
you hear different things.
你会听到不同的事情。
I can't believe he ended up like this.
我不敢相信他的结局是这样的。
Stop taking photos! There are children here.
别再拍照了！这里有孩子。
It's too cruel.
太残忍了。
Good heavens!
我的妈呀！
Damned writers!
该死的作家们！
Is Gicheul finishing school already?
Gicheul 已经完成学业了吗？
No, he's just getting started.
不，他才刚刚开始。
BIO - KWON SEUNGHO
简介 - 权胜浩
"Kwon Seungho".
“权胜浩”。
FACT CHECK CHECK YOUR FATHER'S RECORD
事实核查 检查您父亲的记录
YU EUIJEONG DEPARTMENT SAFETY?
柳义 正部门安全吗？
A POLICEMAN'S WIFE? NAME, PHOTO, DEPARTMENT
警察的妻子？ 姓名、照片、部门
„Yu Euijeong”.
???余义正???.
A photo of your husband?
你丈夫的照片？
I said it was about my father's arrest
我说这是 关于我父亲被捕的事
and they didn't pursue the topic.
他们没有继续这个话题。
But I'm not sure,
但我不确定，
whether they believed me or not.
不管他们是否相信我。
By the way,
顺便一提，
Were you and Jung Gicheul close?
你和郑基哲关系 亲密吗？
For a while in high school.
高中时有一段时间。
I haven't seen him since then.
从那以后我就没见过他。
-Why do you ask? -It's nothing.
-你为什么要问？ -没什么。
I'll call you later.
我一会打给你。
Don't worry.
不用担心。
All right.
好的。
Sorry we didn't mention Detective Park.
抱歉我们没有提到 朴侦探。
Safety considerations.
安全考虑。
Dohyung, I'm disappointed in you.
道亨，我对你很失望。
How do you, of all people,
在所有人中，你如何，
Could you involve Junmo in such a dangerous operation?
这么危险的行动，你能让君莫参与进来吗？
I do not understand this.
我不明白。
I'm sorry, Euijeong.
对不起，义正。
I'm so sorry,
我很抱歉，
but this is something only Junmo can do.
但这是 只有君墨才能做到的事情。
Dohyung.
道亨。
YOUNG GICHEUL
年轻的吉切尔
Jung Gicheul found out that Junmo and I know each other.
郑基哲发现 我和俊模认识。
He also knows I'm a cop.
他也知道我是警察。
Are you really going to keep him there?
你真的要把他留在那里吗？
For now, we should wait for Jung Gicheul's next move.
现在，我们就等待 郑基哲的下一步行动吧。
I'll keep an eye on him
我会关注他
-so don't worry. -Dohyung.
-所以不用担心。 -道亨。
You know Junmo much better than I do.
你比我更了解君莫。
Once he starts something, he will never give up.
一旦他开始做一件事，他就永远不会放弃。
Inspector Yu.
于督察。
You want Detective Park to close this case quickly
你希望朴侦探 尽快结案
and he came home, right?
然后他就回家了，对吗？
To make this happen, we need your help.
为了实现这一目标， 我们需要您的帮助。
Sir, no.
先生，不。
I would be very grateful.
我会很感激。
Did you really have to tell me to come to the office at the crack of dawn?
你真的非要让我 一大早就到办公室吗？
Please. Share with your people.
请。与您的员工分享。
These are American donuts.
这些是美国甜甜圈。
Hold.
抓住。
Thanks for the sweets.
谢谢你的糖果。
No problem. Enjoy your meal.
没问题。请享用。
Good morning sir.
早上好先生。
Hi.
你好。
Kwon Seungh's father, Kwon Jangseok,
权胜的父亲权长石，
he was convicted four times for violating the drug law.
他因违反禁毒法四次被定罪。
As for his schools,
至于他的学校，
I'll check it out in Wonju.
我去原州看看。
Yu Euijeong's father is the former commander of APMS,
柳义正的父亲 是前APMS司令，
Yu Dukhoon. Retired since last year.
于德坤. 从去年开始就退休了。
Her mother is undergoing cancer treatment at Yeongdong Severance Hospital.
她的母亲正在 岭东塞弗兰斯医院接受癌症治疗。
He's in the Security Department,
他在安全部，
and her husband is a detective at Eumseong Police Station.
她的丈夫是阴城警察局的一名侦探。
I have a picture of him here.
我这里有一张他的照片。
Kwon Seungho.
权胜浩.
When you met Euijeong,
当你遇见义正时
did she mention her husband?
她提到她丈夫了吗？
NO.
不。
“Eumseong Police, Criminal Affairs Department.
???阴城警察局 刑事科。
Senior Officer Park Junmo.”
朴俊模 高级警官.???
EUMSEONG POLICE STATION DETECTIVE PARK JUNMO
阴城警察局 侦探朴俊模
Have you seen him before?
你以前见过他吗？
NO.
不。
Take a good look.
好好看看。
You saw him?
你看到他了吗？
I have not seen.
我没见过。
Say.
说。
Who is more handsome? Me or him?
谁更帅？我还是他？
You, boss.
你，老板。
Let's go wash up.
我们去洗漱吧。
Yes sir.
是的先生。
Something else.
还有别的事。
Is Euijeong from Wonju?
Euijeong是原州人吗？
From what I know, she moved there because of her father's job.
据我所知，她搬到那里 是因为她父亲的工作。
Then, when she was in middle school, she returned to Seoul.
然后，当她上中学时， 她回到了首尔。
You didn't know that the police intranet saves your search history,
你不知道警察内网 保存了你的搜索历史记录，
when you log in to the system?
当你登录系统时？
I knew.
我知道。
Then how could you be so reckless
那你怎么可以这么肆无忌惮
to sell this information?
出售这些信息？
I'm sorry, sir.
对不起，先生。
I know your children haven't gotten married yet.
我知道你的孩子 还没有结婚。
-Do you want to get into the newspapers? -No, sir.
-你想上报纸吗？ -不，先生。
From today you will do what I tell you.
从今天起你就按我说的去做。
If you keep up, I'll turn a blind eye to it.
如果你再继续，我就视而不见。
But if you mess up even a little,
但如果你搞砸了哪怕一点点
you're going straight to jail.
你会直接进监狱的。
Yes Sir.
是的先生。
You can go now.
你现在可以离开了。
And always answer my phone.
并且总是接听我的电话。
And he thinks he's the boss.
而且他认为他是老板。
If it weren't for the prior preparations, we would have had problems.
如果没有事先的准备， 我们就会遇到麻烦。
Right.
正确的。
After he scammed the Busan thugs at a rock club
在他在摇滚俱乐部欺骗了釜山暴徒之后
and did a background check right after meeting Inspector Yu,
和余督察见面后就做了背景调查，
it seems that Jung Gicheul is smarter and more meticulous than I thought.
看来郑基哲 比我想象的更聪明、更细心。
Let's see who is smarter.
让我们看看谁更聪明。
How?
如何？
Let's pick up the pace.
让我们加快步伐吧。
By the way, where do you go during the day instead of sleeping?
顺便问一下，你 白天不睡觉的时候去哪里？
I ride the subway and sleep on the seats.
我坐地铁，睡在座位上。
It helps me sleep.
它帮助我睡眠。
Don't say things like that.
别说那样的话。
I feel bad about it now.
我现在感觉很糟糕。
That's not the point.
这不是重点。
Everyone does what they like.
每个人都做自己喜欢的事。
That actually sounds pretty cool.
这实际上听起来很酷。
Why did you start working here?
你为什么开始在这里工作？
Because I wanted to have my life combed.
因为我想梳理一下我的生活。
The world will end in 1999 anyway.
无论如何，世界末日将在1999年到来。
Nostadamus predicted so.
诺斯塔达姆斯如此预测。
Was that the guy's name?
那是那个人的名字吗？
I'm going to have four awesome years
我将度过美好的四年
and I will watch the world end.
我会看着世界末日。
What is?
什么是？
Za bardzo trącę Pokoleniem X?
摩擦力太大 X世代？
Czemu ludzie w tym aucie mają maski?
这车里的人为什么有？？面具？
To cholernie podejrzane.
这真是太可疑了
-Co nie? -Co oni robią?
-哪个没有？ -他们在做什么？？？
Po co mają maski?
他们是做什么用的？？面具？
Co za bydlak.
真是个混蛋。
Szlag!
该死！
Dorwać Jung Gicheula!
多尔瓦？？年轻的吉切拉！
-Hej! -Jung Gicheul, ty bydlaku!
-你好！ ——郑基哲你这个混蛋！
-Wyłaź! -Gdzie Jung Gicheul?
-你和？？！ -郑基哲在哪里？
Wychodź, palancie!
滚出去，你这个混蛋！
Wyłaź stamtąd!
为什么？？和？斯塔？？d！
Wyłączone światła.
关灯。
Co to za dupki?
这些都是些什么混蛋？
Szef jest w środku.
老板在里面。
Kurwa.
斗争。
Szefie, atakują nas.
老大，进攻？？我们。
Weź go ze sobą.
我们？？他们去哭泣吗？
Szefie, chodź ze mną.
老大，来吧？？与我一起？？。
-Szefie! -Tam jest!
-老板！ -有！
Dorwać Jung Gicheula!
多尔瓦？？年轻的吉切拉！
Ja jestem Jung Gicheul!
我是郑基哲！
Chodź tu, sukinsynu!
去？？你这王八蛋！
No chodź!
没有乔德？？！
Chyba wszyscy uciekli.
我想他们都逃跑了。
Szefie, jesteś cały?
老板，你在吗？？所有的？
A ty?
你呢？
Tak.
所以。
Co za skurwysyny.
什么混蛋。
PRZYCHODNIA LEKARSKA SEONGMO
圣模诊所
-Daj mi papierosa. -Tak jest.
-给我一支烟。 -是的先生。
-Ja też chcę. -Proszę.
-我也是？？想？？。 -请？？。
Boli?
他们是？
Nie, wszystko w porządku.
不，一切都很好。
To tylko draśnięcie.
这只是一种刺激。
Co robimy z tym gnojem, Song Donghyukiem?
宋东赫这个混蛋怎么办？
Bo jeśli nic, będzie nas miał za tchórzy.
因为如果什么都没有，他就会拥有我们？太懦弱了。
Może pojedźmy do Busan i zetrzyjmy ich w proch.
也许我们可以去釜山 把它们磨成粉末。
Ja się tym zajmę.
我？？通过那次捕获？？
Proszę pilnować, by rana była sucha.
请？？确保伤口干燥。
-Szwy zdejmiemy za tydzień. -Doktorze.
- 一周后拆线吗？ -医生。
Dobra robota.
好工作。
Zrobiłem tylko to, co należało.
我只做了我必须做的事。
Od jutra w pokoju obok
从明天开始在隔壁房间
będzie czuwał szef Seo. Przepraszam, szefie.
他会看吗？徐老板。 对不起老大。
Ja jestem Jung Gicheul!
我是郑基哲！
Chcę przy sobie Seungho.
想？？胜浩就在他身边。
Szefie, on dopiero co do nas dołączył.
老板，他刚刚加入我们。
Sądzisz, że inni chłopcy tego nie zauważą?
你认为其他男孩不会注意到这一点吗？
I nie możemy trzymać blisko ciebie gościa, który zadaje się z glinami.
而我们无法保留 你附近有一个人 经常出去玩 与警察。
A gdzie byłeś ty albo inni członkowie,
那会是哪里？您或其他成员，
gdy działo się to wszystko?
什么时候发生的事？就这样？
Powiedz.
说。
Rób, co mówię.
切，我还能说什么？
Tak, szefie.
是的先生。
-Yongdae, spocznij. -Tak.
-龙大，休息吧。 -是的。
Załatw mu telefon.
给他一个电话。
-Tak jest. -Hej.
-是的先生。 -你好。
Tak?
所以？
I nowy garnitur.
还有一套新西装。
Tak jest.
是的先生。
Wygląda jak bezdomny.
他看上去就像一个无家可归的人。
Sobie też kup.
这些？？买。
Tak...
所以...
Tak jest! Dziękuję!
是的先生！谢谢你？！
Dohyung. Nasz plan się powiódł.
道亨。我们的计划是 画。
Tak. Od teraz będę jego osobistym ochroniarzem.
是的。从现在开始我会 他的私人保镖。
Dobrze.
好的。
Przy okazji,
顺便一提，
uważam, że byłoby lepiej,
我以为这样会更好
gdybyś nie mówił innym, że Jung Gicheul miał broń.
如果？？我不说 郑基哲的另一个 兄弟？？。
Dobra. Dzięki za cały twój wysiłek.
好的。感谢您的一切努力。
A wtedy ten wielki gość...
然后就大了？？？？？？
-Dobry wieczór.
-晚上好？？
Świetna robota. Usiądźcie.
？？做得好。坐下。
Gładko zaczęliście.
你开始很顺利。
Zatrzymaliście się obok ich auta w idealnym momencie.
你停下来了吗？ 在完美的时刻在他们的车旁边。
Ale ten koleś był naprawdę niezły.
但这家伙？？会 ？？真的吗？？不错。
Udawał, że nas uderzał,
假装要打我们
ale trafiał w ścianę albo podłogę.
但它击中了？在墙壁里？？或地板。
Na udzie mam tylko siniaka. Niesamowite.
我只是大腿上有一块瘀伤。极好的。
Czym on się zajmował?
他在做什么？？忙碌的？？？
To tylko zbir. Zwykły kapuś.
他只是一个暴徒。普通白菜。
Smacznego.
请享用。
Dziękujemy.
谢谢。
Tak jest.
是的先生。
W porządku.
没关系。
Człowieku, nie tam. Tutaj.
伙计，不在那儿。这里。
-Widzisz tamten pokój? -Tak.
-你看到那个房间了吗？ -是的。
Łóżko nad sofą jest twoje. Dobra?
沙发上？？？这是你的。好的？
Tak jest.
是的先生。
Za mną.
为我？？。
Biuro ma zamek na kod.
办公室有密码锁。
Dobrze.
好的。
Jeden, dwa, zero, sześć.
一、二、零、六。
Data moich urodzin.
我的生日。
Co? Nie pasuje ci coś?
什么？你不喜欢什么？？？
Nie, proszę pana. Zapamiętam go.
不谢谢？？先生。我会记住他的。
Tylko zastanawiam się...
我是在想？？...
Co z innymi kodami w drzwiach...
其他的门密码呢...
Boże, jeszcze więcej pytań.
天啊，还有更多问题。
-Słuchaj. -Tak jest.
-听。 -是的先生。
To jedyny kod, który powinieneś znać.
这是您应该使用的唯一代码 知道？？。
Tak jest.
是的先生。
Cześć, tu Seungho. Jak tam sprawy?
大家好，我是胜浩。事情进行得如何？
Tak, u mnie w porządku.
是的，我没事。
Dostałem telefon.
Dosta??em 电话。
Even if they check your chat history,
即使他们检查你的聊天记录，
will turn a blind eye to conversations with "Euijeong".
对与“义正”的对话视而不见。
Call this number from now on.
从现在开始拨打这个号码。
You said your father beat you.
你说你父亲打过你。
Yes sir.
是的先生。
Was he addicted to meth?
他对冰毒上瘾了吗？
So.
所以。
It must have been hard for your mother.
你妈妈一定很辛苦吧。
She left when I was seven.
我七岁时她就离开了。
People like us have similar stories.
像我们这样的人也有类似的故事。
What was it like seeing her after such a long time?
时隔这么久再次见到她是什么感觉？
What do you mean...
你是什​​么意思...
Is Euijeong still laid-back and cool?
义正还是 那么悠闲潇洒吗？
So.
所以。
She should have married a rich man and lived comfortably.
她本应该嫁给一个有钱人 ，过上安逸的生活。
Why did she marry an ordinary village detective?
她为何嫁给 一个普通的乡村侦探？
Come with me.
跟我来。
I'm going out for a while.
我要出去一会儿。
Eat dinner without me.
没有我一起吃晚饭。
Hello.
你好。
Where are you going?
你要去哪里？
The threat may not have passed yet.
威胁可能还没有过去。
We're not done with those bastards from Busan yet .
我们还没有对付那些来自釜山的混蛋。
It would be risky to separate.
分开的话会有风险。
See you.
再见。
Boss.
老板。
We ordered food. Maybe we can talk over dinner?
我们点了食物。 也许我们可以边吃晚饭边聊？
-See you. -See you later, boss.
-再见。 -再见，老板。
Can I ask where we're going?
我可以问一下我们要去哪里吗？
Do Yeongdong Severance.
做永东遣散。
SZPITAL YEONGDONG SEVERANCE
永同市医院隔离区 永 同市医院隔离区
Let's go.
我们走吧。
Euijeong's mother is said to be very sick.
据说义正的母亲病得很重。
We'll say hello.
我们会打招呼。
I will stay here.
我会留在这儿。
You lived next door to them.
你住在他们隔壁。
You should go too.
你也该去吧。
She probably wouldn't remember me anyway.
反正她大概也不会记得我了。
Plus she's sick.
加上她病了。
If I join, she will feel awkward.
如果我加入， 她会感到尴尬。
Go. I'll wait here.
去。我会在这里等。
YOKOHAMA, JAPAN
日本横滨
Your painting skills are amazing.
你的绘画技巧 令人惊叹。
I will definitely frame this painting
我一定会把这幅画装裱起来
and I will hang it in a visible place.
我会把它挂在显眼的地方。
By the way,
顺便一提，
with Jung Gicheul in Seoul...
与郑基哲在首尔...
What is he doing?
他在做什么？
From what I know, he invested in the bars there.
据我所知， 他在那里投资了酒吧。
Well, after we get rid of him,
好吧，当我们摆脱他之后，
I plan to take Gangnam for myself.
我打算把江南据为己有。
But it shouldn't harm my brother.
但这不应该伤害我的兄弟。
Young Gicheul
年轻的吉哲尔
he treats Boss Kanemoto like a father.
他对待金本老板就像对待父亲一样。
I suggest you revise this plan.
我建议你修改一下这个计划。
We are righteous criminals.
我们是正义的罪犯。
But this stray out of nowhere has no respect for order or loyalty
但这不知从何而来的流浪者 不尊重秩序或忠诚
and is chasing money.
并且正在追逐金钱。
Is there any other way?
还有其他办法吗？
First of all, I've already decided.
首先，我已经决定了。
Secondly,
第二，
If I make a decision, I implement it.
如果我做出决定，我就会执行它。
Please convey these words carefully to my brother.
请把这 句话仔细地转达给我的兄弟。
All right.
好的。
So I will.
所以我会。
Once you make a decision, you must act on it
一旦做出决定， 就必须付诸行动
so as not to regret anything.
以免留下任何遗憾。
Oh well...
那好吧...
Sometimes you let dogs in and sometimes you let them out.
有时你让狗进来 ，有时你又让它们出去。
Exactly.
确切地。
Oh my, it's cashmere.
天哪，这是羊绒。
You didn't have to buy such an expensive gift.
你没必要买 这么贵的礼物。
Even on a short walk you should feel warm in it.
即使是短途步行， 您也会感到温暖。
Mimo to...
米莫要...
Gosh, but beautiful.
天哪，但是很漂亮。
Not only is your son-in-law tall and handsome,
你的女婿不但高大帅气，
but he also has a heart of gold.
但他也有一颗金子般的心。
Is everything okay with your mom?
你妈妈一切都好吗？
So.
所以。
What happened to her certainly caused a stir in the church.
她的遭遇 无疑在教会中引起了轰动。
Of course not.
当然不是。
Your mother was so devoted to our church.
你母亲 对我们的教会非常忠诚。
Gicheul.
吉舍尔。
So?
所以？
Couldn't you find another job?
你就不能再找一份工作吗？
So you also think I'm a gangster?
那你也认为 我是黑帮吗？
There are always these rumors about people in the night business.
关于夜店里的人，总是有这样的谣言。
Gossip?
八卦？
So.
所以。
What I do...
我做什么...
It's like an association.
这就像一个协会。
When young people are in the nightclub industry,
当年轻人从事 夜店行业时，
many people start fights with them
许多人开始与他们打架
or looks down on them.
或者看不起他们。
I thought we should help each other.
我想我们应该 互相帮助。
That's why I started my company.
这就是我创办公司的原因。
So you're not doing any bad things?
那你没做什么坏事吧？
Of course not. No worries.
当然不是。不用担心。
Sorry.
对不起。
Halo.
光环。
Yes, father.
是的，父亲。
There's no other way.
没有其他办法了。
Please continue with your plan.
请继续你的计划。
All right.
好的。
Kanemoto, what are you doing?
金本，你在做什么？
Gicheul earns money for me,
Gicheul为我赚钱，
and you, bastard, want to kill him?
而你这个混蛋，却想杀了他？
Kanemoto...
金本...
You bastards.
你这个混蛋。
Damn bastards.
该死的混蛋。
Step back, you motherfuckers!
退后一步，你们这些混蛋！
Hey, you. Drop the weapon.
嘿，你。放下武器。
He's Japanese, so he doesn't understand Korean.
他是日本人， 所以不懂韩语。
It's too dangerous.
太危险了。
Shoot him.
射他。
Kurdish.
库尔德。
Song Donghyuk.
宋东赫.
His father took care of him.
他的父亲照顾他。
Co?
科？
I said I would take care of it. Do you remember?
我说我会处理的。你是否记得？
Petty old bastard. Serves him right.
小气的老混蛋。为他服务是正确的。
Good morning.
早上好。
-Newbie, come here. -Yes Sir.
-新人，过来。 -是的先生。
I see you had a good sleep.
我看你睡得很好。
Your skin is glowing.
你的皮肤容光焕发。
Cholera.
霍乱。
How shiny it is.
多么闪亮啊。
Come in, idiot.
进来吧，白痴。
I don't sweat.
我不流汗。
-Did you pack everything? -Yes.
-你把所有东西都收拾好了吗？ -是的。
Everything packed.
所有东西都装好了。
-Take it. -Yes Sir.
-拿去。 -是的先生。
Take it.
拿去。
Today is a good day, assholes.
今天是个好日子，混蛋们。
-Company dinner. -Yes Sir.
-公司聚餐。 -是的先生。
-Understand? -Yes Sir!
-理解？ -是的先生！
We will do our best.
我们会全力以赴。
Enjoy your meal.
请享用。
-Thank you. -Thank you, boss.
-谢谢。 -谢谢你，老板。
Sorry. Please.
对不起。请。
Enjoy your meal.
请享用。
Can I ask you something?
我能问你一件事吗？
How often does your boss go fishing?
你的老板多久去钓鱼一次？
Several times a month.
一个月几次。
I see.
我懂了。
What should I do when my boss is away?
老板不在时我该怎么办？
Why? Do you want to go on a date?
为什么？你想去约会吗？
Stay at the damn precinct.
留在该死的辖区。
I'm going to have a drink.
我要去喝一杯。
Call me if anything happens.
有什么事就给我打电话。
What an asshole.
真是个混蛋。
How are the waves?
海浪怎么样？
Today is quiet.
今天很安静。
When the boss goes fishing,
老板去钓鱼的时候
when does he usually come back?
他通常什么时候回来？
Sometimes he stays one night.
有时他会住一晚。
Sometimes for two.
有时两个人。
He definitely won't come back today.
他今天肯定不会回来了。
It's late. You're not going to sleep?
现在已经晚了。你不打算睡觉吗？
What's that to you?
那对你来说是什么？
Sweep there.
扫那里。
Let's go somewhere to drink.
我们去个地方喝酒吧。
-Yes Sir.
-是的先生。
Come on.
快点。
The bastard is already drunk.
混蛋已经喝醉了。
Do you want to go too?
你也想去吗？
NO.
不。
-Watch this place. -Yes Sir.
-注意这个地方。 -是的先生。
Have fun.
玩得开心。
BIRTHDAYS OF MEMBERS OF THE GANGNAM UNION
江南工会成员的生日
Cholera.
霍乱。
Euijeong's birthday.
义正生日。
I don't sweat.
我不流汗。
Fucker.
笨蛋。
Nothing exceptional was found with Jung Gicheul ?
郑基哲没有发现什么特别的地方吗？
Correct.
正确的。
But isn't that weird?
但这不是很奇怪吗？
The bastards go fishing several times a month,
这群混蛋 一个月去钓鱼好几次
but there is no fishing rod in the room.
但房间里没有钓鱼竿。
So he may not go fishing.
所以他可能不会去钓鱼。
I'll try to convince him to take me on such a trip.
我会尽力说服他 带我去一次这样的旅行。
METROPOLITAN POLICE, TOKYO
东京都警察厅
Korean boss Song Donghyuk.
韩国老板宋东赫。
According to our Korean sources
据我们的韩国消息人士透露
may be involved in the meth trade.
可能参与冰毒贸易。
He landed in Japan on the 15th at Narita Airport and is now missing.
他于15日抵达日本 成田机场，目前失踪。
His papers were found on the Miura Coast of Kanagawa.
他的文件是 在神奈川县三浦海岸发现的。
We suspect he died nearby
我们怀疑他死在附近
and his body was thrown into the sea.
他的尸体被扔进海里。
From today
从今天开始
we will focus on observation
我们将重点观察
gangsters from Yoshioka-gumi in Tokyo, Chiba and Kanagawa.
来自东京、千叶和神奈川吉冈组的黑帮 。
Understood?
明白了吗？
-Yes Sir!
-是的先生！
Hi.
你好。
DRESSING ROOM
更衣室
Tomatoes.
番茄。
Gangnam Crystal.
江南水晶.
Is it really 99% pure?
真的是99%纯净吗？
Spread the word.
传播这个词。
All right.
好的。
I rach!
我拉赫！
And chop!
还有砍！
What fun.
多有趣啊。
-Turn down the gas? -Turn down the gas.
-关掉煤气灯吗？ -关掉煤气。
Don't kill me!
别杀我！
I'm begging you!
我求你了！
Please don't kill me!
请不要杀我！
Stop.
停止。
Whose goods were you selling until recently?
直到最近您还在销售谁的商品？
Who could it be?
会是谁呢？
This man.
这个男人。
What are you selling now?
你现在卖什么？
The Gangnam Crystal?
江南水晶？
Who is your boss?
你的老板是谁？
I have to meet him.
我必须去见他。
Come here. Raise your head.
过来。抬起头。
Keep it up and your mouth shut.
坚持下去，闭上你的嘴。
Closed!
关闭！
Just a moment.
一会儿。
The last blow.
最后一击。
This huge flashlight is useless.
这个巨大的手电筒没什么用。
Instead of hanging around all day, you could have replaced the batteries.
您不必整天闲逛，而是 可以更换电池。
You didn't buy it, did you?
你没买吧？
Maybe those bastards in Busan dropped it
也许釜山那些混蛋把它扔掉了
when they attacked us in the office.
当他们在办公室袭击我们时。
Are you saying they were cops?
你是说他们是警察吗？
Why would they do that?
他们为什么要那样做？
I don't know.
我不知道。
The cops pretended to be thugs
警察假装成暴徒
and destroyed our office?
并摧毁了我们的办公室？
But why?
但为什么？
Sorry.
对不起。
What's up?
这是怎么回事？
So.
所以。
All right. Wait there.
好的。在那里等着。
Smith.
史密斯.
Yes, Manager Cho?
是吗，曹经理？
Do you think he came alone?
你以为他是一个人来的？
It looks.
它看起来。
Wake up the Kid.
叫醒孩子。
-Cholera. -Where is...
-霍乱。 -哪里...
-Get out of the car. -Get the fuck out.
-从车里出去。 -滚出去。
Come on. Move your ass.
快点。动动你的屁股。
Idiot.
笨蛋。
You have a nice watch.
你有一块漂亮的手表。
Right.
正确的。
Did you come here alone?
你是一个人来这里的吗？
So.
所以。
Child.
孩子。
Hi. Hands.
你好。手。
Let's see...
让我们来看看...
Wait a minute.
等一下。
I just...
我只是...
We can't talk here. Let's go to a secluded place.
我们不能在这里说话。 我们去一个僻静的地方吧。
Sorry.
对不起。
We can't leave a dead body at the elementary school.
我们不能把尸体留 在小学。
The children would be scared.
孩子们会害怕的。
True?
真的？
You are right.
你是对的。
Take him away.
把他带走。
What a great watch.
多么棒的手表啊。
Man, I'm jealous!
老兄，我嫉妒了！
Damn it.
该死的。
Hold. Try it on.
抓住。试试。
And how is it lying?
它又是如何说谎的呢？
What the hell is going on?
这到底是怎么回事？
What is he doing?
他在做什么？
Manager Cho.
曹经理.
Hi! What the fuck are you doing?
你好！你他妈在做什么？
What the fuck?
搞什么鬼？
Child. Go check it out.
孩子。去看看吧。
My neck hurts.
我的脖子疼。
Go to hell!
去死吧！
Hey, miss!
嘿，小姐！
Get out of the car! My neck was hurting!
从车里出去！我的脖子很痛！
Miss!
错过！
What?
什么？
What the fuck?
搞什么鬼？
I can not see!
我看不见！
Fight!
斗争！
You fucking...
你他妈的...
Kwon Seungho.
权胜浩.
So?
所以？
Hello.
你好。
Come with me.
跟我来。
Come on.
快点。
Hello.
你好。
Who let you wear such fancy pants, dickhead?
谁让你穿 这么花哨的裤子，白痴？
You fucking bastard.
你他妈的混蛋。
Hello.
你好。
Skurwysyn.
斯库维森。
Come on.
快点。
Reply.
回复。
Who's that?
那是谁？
Hi.
你好。
What an ass he is.
他真是个混蛋。
He tried to kill the boss
他试图杀死老板
and ruin our business.
并毁了我们的生意。
What will we do with him?
我们要对他做什么？
Zabijmy go.
扎比吉米走吧。
Which did not? Do you think so too?
哪个没有？你也这么认为吗？
Ty sukinsynu.
泰·苏金西努。
It is not you?
不是你吗？
So why are we doing this?
那么我们为什么要这样做呢？
You think there's no reason?
你觉得没有理由吗？
-NO? -Stop shaking, bitch.
-不？ -别发抖了，婊子。
You son of a bitch.
你个王八蛋。
Raise your head.
抬起头。
Fucking shit.
他妈的狗屎。
Hold him.
抓住他。
Hello.
你好。
Come on.
快点。
Raise your hands.
举起你的手。
Hold him tight.
紧紧抱住他。
One two Three.
一二三。
And this was supposed to kill him?
这就是要杀了他吗？
Then try it yourself.
然后自己尝试一下。
Do you like it or what?
你喜欢它还是什么？
Then do it yourself, son of a bitch.
那就自己动手吧，混蛋。
Pick it up.
捡起来。
I'll hit him here.
我就在这里打他。
Into this place.
进入这个地方。
Jebana likes it.
杰巴娜喜欢它。
You son of a bitch.
你个王八蛋。
Don't tense up, bitch.
别紧张，贱人。
This bitch deserves a spanking for her nice underwear.
这个婊子因为她漂亮的内衣就应该被打屁股。
Come here.
过来。
Time to spank, bitch.
是时候打屁股了，婊子。
Once.
一次。
Two.
二。
Once again.
再次。
-Three. -Enough.
-三。 -足够的。
Enough of this fun. We're finishing this.
这种乐趣已经够了。我们正在完成这个。
Yes sir.
是的先生。
You finish it.
你完成它。
So that I can trust you.
这样我才能信任你。
Shoot him.
射他。
Shoot.
射击。
Cholera.
霍乱。
Shoot!
射击！
Fighting.
斗争。
Subtitles: Grzegorz Marczyk
字幕：格热戈日·马尔奇克